Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Labels (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Acconci, Vito (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Art Workers Coalition [Photocopies] (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Burden, Chris (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - "Degenerate Art," Nazi Art Show (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Gomez-Pena, Guillermo (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Guerilla Art Action Group (GAAG) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Hammons, David (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Hoffman, Abbie (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Hseih, Tehching (Sam), 1974, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Maciunas, George (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1975, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Monnig, Peter, 1982 - 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Moorman, Charlotte, 1967, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Nenner, Paulette, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Oppenheim, Dennis (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - The People's Flag Show, 1970 - 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Real Estate Show, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Schneemann, Carolee, 1985, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Scott, Dread, 1989 - 1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Artists - Wodiczko, Krzysztof, 1985, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Press Clippings (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Travel - Fact Sheet (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Travel - Checklist, 1990, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Travel - Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Travel - Western Gallery (Washington), November - December 1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Illegal America [1990.02]: Exhibition Travel - Otis Art Institute (California), June - September 1991 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Invitations, April 28, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Press Kit (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Biographical Information, 1990, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Correspondence, 1990, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Exhibition Checklist and Floor Plan (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Installation Notes (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Exhibition Wall Text, April 28, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Precario / Precarious by Cecilia Vicuña [3 copies], 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Press Clippings (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Catalogue Text (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cecilia Vicuna: Precarious [1990.03]: Catalogue Orders (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: Posters [Invitations, Slide], May 11, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: "Internal Exile: New Films From Chile" Exhibition Schedule, May 4 - 7 [1990] (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: Video Information (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: Video Program, April - May 1990 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: Installation Information (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Internal Exile [1990.04]: Press Clippings, May 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Invitations, June 1, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Press Release, June 1, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Artists' Contracts (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Correspondence, May 1990 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Performance Schedule, [June 1, 1990] (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Stuart Anthony's Notes, [June 1990] (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Rental Information, May 1990 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Installation Information, [June 1990] (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Release Forms, June 1, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Tantrum [1990.05]: Press Clipping - The Village Voice, June 5, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Invitations, June 9, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Biographical Information (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Correspondence, 1987 - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Loan Information, 1987, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Exhibition Checklist, Wall Labels, [June 1990] (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Price List, [June 1990] (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Curatorial Text by Papo Colo, [June 1990] (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Exhibition Fact Sheet and Budget, February 1990 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Jacques Roch [1990.06]: Press Clipping - The New Yorker, July 9, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Invitations, September 8, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Biographical Information (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Contract, April, June 1990 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Correspondence, 1989 - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Price List (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Press Clippings (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Catalogue Essays, 1989 - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Exhibition Travel Fact Sheet and Schedule (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Exhibition Travel - Walker Art Center (Minneapolis), March 4 - May 6, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds [1990.07]: Exhibition Travel - San Jose Museum of Art, October 15 - December 30, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Invitations, October 13, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Biographical Information (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Correspondence, 1983 - 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Loan Information (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Exhibition Checklist, October 13, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Price List, October 13, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Exhibition Labels and Notes (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Sales / Reserves, 1990 - 1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Press Clippings (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Adrian Piper: Why Guess [1990.08]: Catalogue Essays, June 1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Research Materials (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Funding - NYSCA Proposal, July 1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Invitations, November 7, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Invitation Letters, October 6, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Press Release, November 7, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Biographical Information - Keith J. Sanborn, Curator (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Correspondence, 1989 - 1990 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Loan Information (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Film Lists, November 7 - 10, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Film Transcripts, 1975, 1978, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Program (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Translations by Keith Sanborn, November 7 - 10, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Text by Tom Levin, Project Curator (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Photo Captions / Wall Text (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Equipment Loan Information, October - November 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Installation Notes, November 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Attendance / Box Office, November 7 - 10, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Film Modernism and Its Discontents [1990.09]: Press Clipping - The Village Voice, November 13, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Invitations [with slide], November 17, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Press Release, November 17, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Biographical Information (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Correspondence, 1990 - 1991, 1998 - 1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Loan Information (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Photodocumentation Loans (Press), November 17, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Condition Reports, September 6, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Shipping Information, 1990 - 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Price List (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Exhibition Labels (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Public Program - ITSOFOMO Performance, December 7 - 10, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Sales / Reserves, 1990 - 1991 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: ACT UP Benefit Sales, 1990 - 1991 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Dinner Party, December 11, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: AICA Best Gallery Shows 1990 - 1991 [Press Release], September 12, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Press Clippings, 1990 - 1991 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - David Wojnarowicz: Tongues of Flame [1990.10]: Catalogue Requests, 1990 - 1991 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Invitations, February 2, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Press Kits, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Biographical Information (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Correspondence, 1991 - 1992, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Loan Information (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Shipping Information, January - March 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Exhibition Checklist, February 2 - March 19, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Price List, February 2 - March 19, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Press Clippings (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Catalogue - Interview with Fay by J. Ingberman (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Catalogue - Requests, February 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Ming Fay: Nature Reborn [1991.01]: Traveling Exhibition Fact Sheet (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Invitations, April 6, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Press Release, April 6, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Press Kits, April 6, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Artist's Statement, March 1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Biographical Information
    General note
    This file includes:
    Rand, Archie and John Yau. Mug City Moves. A Monkey Choir Maestros Production: New York, NY. 1991.
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Correspondence, 1990 - 1991 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Complete Letter Paintings Checklist (Reference) (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Reference List of Musicians and Songs (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Shipping Information (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Exhibition Checklist, April 6, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Price List, April 6, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Exhibition Labels (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Music Script (Audio Tapes) (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Dinner Party Information, May 13, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Press Clippings (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Catalogue - Essay by John Yau (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Archie Rand: The Letter Paintings [1991.02]: Catalogue - Requests (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Invitations, May 29, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Press Release, May 29, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Press Kits, May 29, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Biographical Information (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Project Description (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Correspondence, 1990 - 1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Shipping Information (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Installation Instructions (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Exhibition Checklist, May 29, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Interview Questions for Visitors (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Jaime Davidovich: Forces/Farces [1991.03]: Press Clippings, 1983, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Invitations, September 7, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Press Release, September 7, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Biographical Information (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Loan Information (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Exhibition Checklist, September 7, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Price List, September 7, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Dinner Party Information, October 14, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Sales /Reserves, 1991 - 1992 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: AICA Best Gallery Shows, 1991 - 1992 [Press Release], December 20, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Press Clippings, 1991 - 1992 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Catalogue Information (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Nancy Grossman [1991.04]: Catalogue Requests (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Parallel History Press Release (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: The Hybrid State Press Release, November 2, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Wall Text (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Correspondence, 1991 - 1992 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Shipping Information (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Musical Performers, 1988 - 1991 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Press Clippings (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - "Wonderbread and Spanglish Art" and "Cultural Identities Before and After the Exit of Bureau-communism" by Luis Camnitzer, 1991, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - "Institutionalized Repression of Cultural Difference: The Fractious Hybrid State (Of Things)" by Joshua Decter [Essay with Correspondence], 1992 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - "Legal Aliens" by Jimmie Durham, November 26, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - "From Art-Maggeddon to Gringostroica" by Guillermo Gómez-Peña (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - "From Pastiche to Macaroni" and "Tupinicopolis: The City of Retrofuturistic Indians" by Celeste Olaquiaga, [1991 - 1992] (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - "Beyond the Hybrid State? (De)mobilization" by Krzysztof Wodiczko [Drafts and Correspondence], 1992 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - Artist Statements, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Catalogue - Orders, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - The Hybrid State (Parallel History) [1991.05]: Exhibition Travel - CU Art Galleries (Colorado), 1991 - 1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Research Materials, 1988 - 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Program Proposal, November 9, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Invitations, November 6, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Press Release, November 6, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Biographical Information - Juliana Emilia Fusco Miyares (Coco Fusco), Curator (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Contract - Anthology Film Archives, September 25, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Film Distributors and Fees (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Correspondence - Requests for Review Tapes (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Correspondence - [Program Coordination] (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Films and Filmmakers (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Screening Schedule / Program, November 6 - 17, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Advertising (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Cocktail Party Information, October 1991 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Film Return Information, November 1991 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Box Office Totals, November 6 - 17, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Press Clippings, 1991 - 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Catalogue - Essays (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - The Hybrid State Films (Parallel History) [1991.06]: Catalogue - Proofs (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: NYSCA Grant Proposal (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Research Materials, 1991 - 1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Invitations, January 17, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Correspondence, January 1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Production Notes, [January 1992] (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Performances - Sud-acá / SUDACA, January 17, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Performances - Pinoy Tok, January 18, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Comp Lists, [January 1992] (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Press Clipping - C. Carr for The Village Voice, January 21, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Speaking Tongues [1992.01]: Insurance Claim for Stolen Equipment (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Invitations, February 1, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Biographical Information (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Correspondence, January - June 1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Loan Forms, January 1992 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Shipping Information, March 18, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Exhibition Checklist, February 1, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Price List, February 1, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Artwork (Photocopies) (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Public Programs - "Your House is Mine" Reading, March 4, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - John Fekner: Remnant Memory [1992.02]: Press Clippings (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Invitations, March 28, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Press Release / Listing, March 28, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Biographical Information (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Contract, September 9, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Correspondence, 1991 - 1992 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Exhibition Checklist, March 28, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Price List, March 28, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Shipping Information, March 30, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Sales / Reserves, 1992 - 1993, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Attendance Information, April 1992 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Deinstallation Checklist / Photo List (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Press Clippings (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Catalogue - Interview with Birch by J. Ingberman (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Catalogue - P. Colo's Introduction, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Catalogue - "Gumbo, Ya/ya, and Hey Pocky Way: Willie Birch's New Orleans and African Americans Making it What it is" by William Fagaly, 1991 - 1992 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Catalogue - Proofs, June 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Catalogue - Requests, July 1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Exhibition Travel - Fact Sheet, March - April 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Willie Birch [1992.03]: Exhibition Travel - Correspondence, 1992 - 1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)